Guide to the Time Inc. Records Overview 1853-2015 MS 3009
New-York Historical Society
- RG 44. Time Inc. Time Canada Ltd. Records (1954-1975, 1995-1999)
  The Time Canada Ltd. Records contain the records from the business side of the subsidiary of Time Inc. that published the Canadian edition of Time. Records are primarily from President Don Brown, and Managing Directors Lawrence Laybourne, Steve LaRue, and Bradley Gundy. There are a few folders of operating statements and from the Promotion Department.
  Click here to link to the Guide to the Time Inc. Time Canada Ltd. Records.